[
    {
        "Question": "manifestations",
        "Answer": "expressions",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exhibit",
        "Answer": "display",
        "Options": "show"
    },
    {
        "Question": "rigors",
        "Answer": "difficulties",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "solely",
        "Answer": "only",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "legitimately",
        "Answer": "officially",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "devised",
        "Answer": "created",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dispensable",
        "Answer": "not necessary",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "air",
        "Answer": "feeling",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "gratify",
        "Answer": "satisfy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "rely",
        "Answer": "depend",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "innumerable",
        "Answer": "countless",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "signature",
        "Answer": "identifying mark",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dormant",
        "Answer": "inactive",
        "Options": "hibernated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "perceived",
        "Answer": "seen",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "no wander",
        "Answer": "unsurprising",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "extraneous",
        "Answer": "from outside",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dissuade",
        "Answer": "discourage",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "bulk",
        "Answer": "mass",
        "Options": "largest part"
    },
    {
        "Question": "exhausting",
        "Answer": "extremely tiring",
        "Options": "use up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "penchant",
        "Answer": "inclination",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "insights into",
        "Answer": "an understanding of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "adequately",
        "Answer": "sufficiently",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fragile",
        "Answer": "easily damaged",
        "Options": "delicate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "provoked",
        "Answer": "brought about",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "viability",
        "Answer": "ability to exist",
        "Options": "surrounding area"
    },
    {
        "Question": "durable",
        "Answer": "long lasting",
        "Options": "existing for a long time without significant damage"
    },
    {
        "Question": "coinage",
        "Answer": "creation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "estimate",
        "Answer": "projection",
        "Options": "evaluate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "drastically",
        "Answer": "extensively",
        "Options": "severely/ extremely"
    },
    {
        "Question": "giant",
        "Answer": "huge",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "episodes",
        "Answer": "occurrence",
        "Options": "a series of events"
    },
    {
        "Question": "contour",
        "Answer": "outline",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "criteria",
        "Answer": "standards",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "feat",
        "Answer": "remarkable achievement",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exceptional",
        "Answer": "extraordinary",
        "Options": "unusual"
    },
    {
        "Question": "distinct",
        "Answer": "separate/ differ",
        "Options": "clear"
    },
    {
        "Question": "continuous",
        "Answer": "uninterrupted",
        "Options": "constant"
    },
    {
        "Question": "contiguous",
        "Answer": "neighboring",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "controversial",
        "Answer": "debatable/ conflict",
        "Options": "producing disagreement"
    },
    {
        "Question": "exploit",
        "Answer": "use to advantage/ taking advantage of",
        "Options": "utilize"
    },
    {
        "Question": "consensus",
        "Answer": "agreement",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "consumed",
        "Answer": "used up",
        "Options": "eat up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "chronology",
        "Answer": "a list that pairs events with dates",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "domestic",
        "Answer": "household",
        "Options": "home"
    },
    {
        "Question": "monumental",
        "Answer": "enormous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sustain",
        "Answer": "support/ maintain",
        "Options": "continue/ uninterrupted"
    },
    {
        "Question": "consider",
        "Answer": "think about",
        "Options": "view as"
    },
    {
        "Question": "several simultaneous developments",
        "Answer": "developments that occurred at the same time",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enlist",
        "Answer": "assist",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "autonomy",
        "Answer": "independence",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "presumably",
        "Answer": "it is reasonable to assume",
        "Options": "supposedly"
    },
    {
        "Question": "objective",
        "Answer": "purpose",
        "Options": "unbiased"
    },
    {
        "Question": "copious",
        "Answer": "abundant",
        "Options": "plentiful"
    },
    {
        "Question": "flexible",
        "Answer": "adaptable",
        "Options": "bendable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "alternate",
        "Answer": "take turns at",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "branch",
        "Answer": "division",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "arid",
        "Answer": "dry",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "end",
        "Answer": "purpose",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "give rise to",
        "Answer": "produce",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "perspective",
        "Answer": "viewpoint",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dispute",
        "Answer": "argument",
        "Options": "contention"
    },
    {
        "Question": "comprehensive",
        "Answer": "thorough/ complete",
        "Options": "understandable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "crucial",
        "Answer": "important",
        "Options": "decisively"
    },
    {
        "Question": "neglected",
        "Answer": "failed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dramatic",
        "Answer": "striking",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pristine",
        "Answer": "pure",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "acclaimed",
        "Answer": "praisable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "profile",
        "Answer": "view from side",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dam",
        "Answer": "block",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accumulation",
        "Answer": "build up/ deposits",
        "Options": "increasing"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compounded",
        "Answer": "added to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "securing",
        "Answer": "getting",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "conspicuous",
        "Answer": "noticeable",
        "Options": "clearly visible"
    },
    {
        "Question": "assume",
        "Answer": "believe",
        "Options": "suppose"
    },
    {
        "Question": "bizarre",
        "Answer": "odd",
        "Options": "very strange"
    },
    {
        "Question": "beforehand",
        "Answer": "foreordain",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enigmatic",
        "Answer": "mysterious",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "scores",
        "Answer": "large numbers",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "concede",
        "Answer": "accept",
        "Options": "admit"
    },
    {
        "Question": "disposition",
        "Answer": "temperament",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "upon reflection",
        "Answer": "after consideration",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "overtaxed",
        "Answer": "heavily burdened",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "affair",
        "Answer": "matter",
        "Options": "event"
    },
    {
        "Question": "integral",
        "Answer": "essential",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "anxiety",
        "Answer": "worry",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ascend",
        "Answer": "go up",
        "Options": "climbing"
    },
    {
        "Question": "classic",
        "Answer": "typical",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exaggerate",
        "Answer": "overstate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "imaginative",
        "Answer": "creative",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "speculates",
        "Answer": "puts forward as possibility",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "by and large",
        "Answer": "for the most part",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "adverse",
        "Answer": "harmful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "overall",
        "Answer": "general",
        "Options": "considered as a whole"
    }
]